https://greenronin.com/green-ronin-publishing-privacy-policy/

Green Ronin Publishing Privacy Policy[last updated April 1, 2019]Green Ronin Publishing has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our web sites, GreenRonin.com, RoninArmy.com, and other Green Ronin sites hosted on this server and pointing to this Privacy Policy.Green Ronin’s Pledge to Our CustomersGreen Ronin Publishing respects your privacy. We do not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information regarding our customers to any third party. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented.Who We AreGreen Ronin Publishing, LLC, herein also referred to as “Green Ronin,” “we,” “us,” and “our,” is a small publishing company based in Seattle, Washington, USA, which contracts creative and technically-skilled freelancers in the United States and elsewhere in the world to create tabletop games and supplements and related fiction.For privacy-related concerns, please email us at custserv+privacy@greenronin.com or contact us via post at:Green Ronin Publishing 3815 S. Othello St. Suite 100, #311 Seattle, WA 98118 USAWe very much appreciate you being a part of the Green Ronin community, and for commenting on our forums or contacting us through our web sites. We take safeguarding your personal information and respecting your right to privacy very seriously. If you have any questions about our privacy policy and/or practices, please email us at custserv+privacy@greenronin.com. If you disagree with any of the terms spelled out in this privacy policy, please stop using our web sites and services.Use of InformationGreen Ronin will not collect any personal information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. Examples of such information are: name, postal address, email address, phone number, and product commentary.Green Ronin Publishing may share non-personal aggregate, or summary, information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties, but Green Ronin does not sell or share any information at the individual customer level.Green Ronin Publishing recommends that if you are providing information on behalf of a child, that you use the child’s parent or guardian’s email address and that you have the permission of that child’s parent or guardian.What Information Do We Gather About You?Our message board system stores your IP address, but in general we do not make any use of that information. IP addresses may be used at our discretion to block offensive messages or posters from our message board system, in order to protect our customers and uphold our community standards. (An IP address is a set of numbers used by Web servers to route information over the Internet to a specific server or machine.)GreenRonin.com features a moderated message board system wherein customers may post questions about our products. This forum could also be used by customers to post personal contact information, but such use is not required or advised by Green Ronin Publishing. The system provides the option of including an email address, but this information is not required. Age screening is in place in our message board system, per COPPA requirements.Site Usage Guidelines for ChildrenWe at Green Ronin Publishing are concerned about helping keep the Internet a safe place for everyone, but especially for children. GreenRonin.com:Will never collect online contact information from children without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, such online information will only be used to respond directly to the child’s request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent.Will never collect personally identifiable offline contact information from children without prior parental consent.Never distributes to third parties any personally identifiable information, from children or adults.Does provide a forum wherein children or adults might publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information, but we do not require or condone such use of our message board system.Will never entice children to divulge more information than is needed to participate in activities on our Web site, by the prospect of a special game, prize, or other activity.Green Ronin Publishing will not be liable for any damages that may result from misrepresentation of age by a user of our Web site.Choice/Opt-OutWe do not use our customers’ contact information for any communication other than directly responding to specific customer service questions. We do not store customers’ contact information, except if deliberately entered by the customer into messages on our message board system. This site gives users the following options for asking us to remove their contact information from our message board system:send email to: custserv+privacy@greenronin.comwrite us: 3815 S. Othello St. Suite 100, #311, Seattle, WA 98118, USAChange/ModifyThis site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.send email to: custserv@greenronin.comwrite us: 3815 S. Othello St. Suite 100, #311, Seattle, WA 98118, USAContacting UsIf you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:Customer Service Green Ronin Publishing 3815 S. Othello St. Suite 100, #311 Seattle, WA 98118 USA custserv@greenronin.comGreen Ronin PublishingNisaba Press (GR Fiction)Green Ronin Online StoreGreen Ronin Gift ShopGreen Ronin SitesGreen Ronin PublishingNisaba Press FictionModern AGE RPGFantasy AGE RPGBlue Rose RPGDragon Age RPGMutants & MastermindsGreen Ronin Online StoreGreen Ronin Gift ShopConnect With Green RoninContact Green Ronin@GreenRoninPub on TwitterGreenRonin on FacebookOur YouTube ChannelGreenRoninPublishing on TwitchGRAADS: Green Ronin AGE Appropriate Discord ServerFreedom City: A Mutants & Masterminds Discord ServerPolicies[Proposal] S.T.O.P. Harassment (Standards, Terms, and Other Practices)Privacy PolicySubmissions PolicyStore Return PolicyForum Terms of ServiceCopyright Protection PolicyArchives Archives Select Month December 2020 November 2020 October 2020 September 2020 August 2020 July 2020 June 2020 May 2020 April 2020 March 2020 February 2020 January 2020 December 2019 November 2019 October 2019 September 2019 August 2019 July 2019 June 2019 May 2019 April 2019 March 2019 February 2019 January 2019 December 2018 November 2018 October 2018 September 2018 August 2018 July 2018 June 2018 May 2018 April 2018 March 2018 February 2018 January 2018 December 2017 November 2017 October 2017 September 2017 August 2017 July 2017 June 2017 May 2017 April 2017 March 2017 February 2017 January 2017 December 2016 November 2016 October 2016 September 2016 August 2016 July 2016 June 2016 May 2016 April 2016 March 2016 February 2016 January 2016 December 2015 November 2015 October 2015 September 2015 August 2015 July 2015 June 2015 May 2015 April 2015 March 2015 February 2015 January 2015 December 2014 November 2014 October 2014 September 2014 August 2014 July 2014 June 2014 May 2014 April 2014 March 2014 February 2014 January 2014 December 2013 November 2013 October 2013 September 2013 August 2013 July 2013 June 2013 May 2013 April 2013 March 2013 February 2013 January 2013 December 2012 November 2012 October 2012 September 2012 August 2012 July 2012 June 2012 May 2012 April 2012 March 2012 February 2012 January 2012 December 2011 November 2011 October 2011 September 2011 August 2011 July 2011 June 2011 May 2011 April 2011 March 2011 February 2011 January 2011 December 2010 November 2010 October 2010 September 2010 August 2010 July 2010 June 2010 May 2010 April 2010 March 2010 February 2010 January 2010 December 2009 November 2009 October 2009 September 2009 August 2009 July 2009 June 2009 May 2009 April 2009 March 2009 February 2009 January 2009 December 2008 November 2008 October 2008 September 2008 August 2008 July 2008 June 2008 May 2008 April 2008 March 2008 February 2008 January 2008 December 2007 November 2007 October 2007 September 2007 August 2007 July 2007 June 2007 May 2007 April 2007 March 2007 February 2007 January 2007 December 2006 November 2006 October 2006 September 2006 August 2006 July 2006 June 2006 May 2006 April 2006 March 2006 February 2006 January 2006 December 2005 November 2005 October 2005 September 2005 August 2005 July 2005 June 2005 May 2005 April 2005 March 2005 February 2005 January 2005 December 2004
CategoriesCategoriesSelect CategoryA Song of Ice and Fire Roleplaying NewsAGE RPGBlue Rose RPG NewsCard GamesChronicle SystemCritical RoleDC Adventures NewsDragon Age RPG NewsEvents: FreebooterEvents: Green Ronin OfficialEvents: Staff AppearancesFantasy AGEFifth EditionFreeportGreen Ronin NewsGreen Ronin PresentsModern AGE RPGMutants & Masterminds NewsNisaba Press (Fiction)Ork!PathfinderPirate’s Port: Freebooter NewsPodcastRonin ReportRonin Round TableSentinels of Earth-PrimeThe Expanse RPGThe Lost CitadelTitansgraveTrue20 news
